http://www.harborstone.com/home/why-harborstone/security#privacy

Rewards Programs
Quicklinks:
Real Estate Center
Quicklinks:
Business Services
Quicklinks:
Resources
Quicklinks:
Financial Calculators
Quicklinks:
Security
At Harborstone, we know that your personal financial information is an asset worth protecting. In addition to the activities we do to keep your information secure, we can help you stay informed about the latest scams—and how to avoid them.
Current Alerts Account Protection Privacy Policy Security Articles Other Resources Security Standards
CURRENT ALERTS
Real-Time Security and Fraud Alerts
In a time when fraud, scams, and identity theft are a real concern, Harborstone uses the latest security protocols to ensure that your financial transactions and personal data remain confidential. We will keep you updated about the latest scamming tactics to help increase awareness of security issues.
Fraud Alert: Phone Calls Asking for Personal Information
We have received reports of fake phone calls from fraudsters posing as Harborstone employees, asking members to verify or disclose personal sensitive information.
These calls are not legitimate and may even sometimes appear to come from Harborstone. We advise you to never give out your personal information unless you are positive that it’s to a trusted source. If you feel that you may have provided your personal information to these fraudsters or another untrusted source, please call us immediately.
If you receive a phone call that you are suspicious of, please hang up and dial the number to call us at (253) 584-2260 or 1-800-523-3641 to verify the validity of the call.
(253) 584-2260
1-800-523-3641
Tweets by Harborstone
ACCOUNT PROTECTION
How We Protect Your Account
Our members' account and personal information security is our top priority.
REST ASSURED KNOWING:
You do not need to call us unless you see transactions you do not recognize. We are actively using our fraud-monitoring tools to look for abnormal transactions or spending and ATM patterns—and to help us block these transactions.
We will let you know if we see unusual activity on your account.
We will send you a new card if we determine that to be necessary.
We regularly monitor Harborstone member accounts for unusual activity and encourage you to check your account activity using online, mobile, and telephone banking, as well as text and email alerts.
We will call you to verify transaction information only. If you receive a phone call from someone saying they are from Harborstone and asking for sensitive account information, please hang up and notify us immediately by calling trusted, official Harborstone phone numbers.
WHAT YOU CAN DO:
Continue using your Harborstone card(s).
Make sure that your contact information is updated so that important account information and new debit or ATM cards are not being sent to the wrong address. You'll also want to notify us when you have a change in your phone number or email address. This will allow us to appropriately contact you when necessary.
Switch to eStatements, get email alerts when your statement becomes available, and relax knowing your account information is safe and secure.
Familiarize yourself with Harborstone's online banking security standards.
Regularly check your credit report. You can check your credit easily online, and doing so can help catch signs of identity theft. We recommend using AnnualCreditReport.com or each of the three national credit reporting agencies (Experian, Equifax, and TransUnion) once every 12 months.
WHO TO CONTACT:
If you find yourself in one of the following situations, we're here to help. Give us a call.
(253) 584-2260
1-800-523-3641
To report a lost or stolen debit card or for general questions regarding your debit card
To initiate a fraud claim or a transaction dispute on your debit card
To report a lost or stolen personal credit card
To report a lost or stolen business credit card
Identity Theft or Misuse of Your Personal Information
If you believe you are the victim of identity theft or have reason to believe your personal information has been misused, you should immediately contact the Federal Trade Commission and/or the Office of the Attorney General in your home state. You can obtain information from these sources about steps an individual can take to avoid identity theft as well as information about fraud alerts and security freezes. You should also contact your local law enforcement authorities and file a police report. Obtain a copy of the police report in case you are asked to provide copies to creditors to correct your records.
Federal Trade Commission
FTC.gov/IDTheft
1-877-438-4338
600 Pennsylvania Ave. NW
Washington, DC 20580
Office of the Attorney General
Washington State, ATG.WA.gov
(360) 753-6200
P.O. Box 40100
Olympia, WA 98504
PRIVACY POLICY
We respect the privacy of our members and recognize the importance of maintaining the confidentiality of your personal financial information. Our privacy policy outlines what Harborstone does with your personal information.
Privacy Policy
SECURITY ARTICLES
Each month, we highlight a different digital security concern to arm you with the best practices when it comes to using technology.
Don’t Get Ripped Off in Romance
Read Article
Renters Beware
Read Article
Scammers Posing as Loved Ones
Read Article
Online Loan Applications Gone Wrong
Read Article
Secret Shopper Hoax
Read Article
SSN Scams Are on the Rise
Read Article
OTHER RESOURCES
The following are non-Harborstone resources that may also be helpful in preventing identity theft or handling it should you find yourself a victim.
Annual
Credit Report
Visit Site
Credit
Bureau—Experian
Visit Site
Credit
Bureau—Equifax
SECURITY STANDARDS
We care deeply about keeping your money safe while providing you with easy access to your accounts. With the continued growth of online banking and mobile apps, there are increased needs for greater security standards to keep you and your money well protected. Here are answers to some of the most frequently asked questions regarding security.
Not seeing your question? Try a search.
Open an Account
Copyright © 2020 Harborstone Credit Union
All rights reserved.
